说来真奇怪  人们总是来漫画书店买书
It's amazing people keep coming to comic book stores
而不是直接从网上下载电子版的
instead of just downloading comics digitally.
这样可能更好
It's probably for the best.
对于很多宅男来说  这里是每周出门的唯一理由
For a lot of these guys, the weekly trip here
他们妈妈也好抓紧自己儿子唯一挪窝的时间
is the only chance their mom has to go down
冲进房间换上干净的床单
to the basement and change their sheets.
这倒提醒我  我今晚有干净的新床单睡了
Oh, that reminds me, I get fresh sheets tonight. Yay.
怎么样
Well?
感觉新漫画书之夜如何
What do you think of New Comic Book Night?
很神奇吧
Magic, huh?
谢尔顿  我其实很失望
Sheldon, I'm disappointed.
作为一个天才
As a brilliant man,
你也算数一数二的人物
you're entitled to a vice.
我能理解你经常逛鸦片窑
I could understand frequenting an opium den
或是为了好玩去猎杀你的同伴
or hunting your fellow man for sport.
但是看漫画  逊咖
But this? Lame-o.
首先  漫画书通过连环画来讲述故事
Well, A) Comic books employ storytelling through sequential art,
这种方式可追溯到一万七千年前
an medium that dates back 17,000 years
拉斯科洞穴壁画时代
to the cave paintings of Lascaux,
其次  你还玩竖琴呢
and B) You play the harp.
你以为那很酷吗
Like that's cool.
要我帮你找漫画吗
Can I help you find anything?
有没有描述一个女人的乳房
A comic that depicts a woman whose bosom
不能用来当救生装置的漫画
can't be used as a flotation device.
抱歉  来这里的男生
Sorry. Most of the guys
大部分都喜欢大咪咪
who come in here like big boobs.
有几个自己的咪咪也挺大的
Couple of them have big boobs.
"卡亚战神"出了新的扩展包
The new Warlords of Ka'a expansion pack is out.
又出新的  有没有搞错
A new one? Unbelievable.
这帮人老是瞎掰一些新的怪物
They just keep making up more cheesy monsters,
把它们印到卡上  一包卖25块钱
slapping them on cards and selling them at 25 bucks a pop.
这是在暗中让没女人的宅男多掏一份税钱
It's like a secret tax on guys who can't get laid.
他们真是太不给力了
They're not even trying.
还记得那个有"地狱大象"的"邪恶撒旦"包吗
Remember the Satanimals pack with the Hellephant?
太扯淡了
Why, absurd.
他算个啥  死了以后下地狱的邪恶大象吗
What was he, a bad elephant who died and went to hell?
一头大象能干出啥坏事
What could an elephant possibly do
死了以后还要被打下地狱
that would cause him eternal damnation?
"狂野西部女巫"
"Wild West and Witches"?
有哪个白痴会关心
What kind of loser cares about a showdown
比利小子和北方白袍巫师的决战
between Billy the Kid and the White Wizard of the North?
只有窝囊废才关心
A total loser.
不就是一个手持六发左轮手枪的小子
Obviously, a guy with a six-shooter
打败了一个手持魔杖的老人嘛
beats an old man with a magic wand.
等等
Well, h-hold on.
要是那个巫师
Uh, what if the wizard casts
在比利小子的牛仔帽上下了困惑头盔咒呢
a Helmet of Confusion spell on Billy the Kid's cowboy hat?
什么  拜托
What? Please!
我们说的可是比利小子
This is Billy the Kid we're talking about.
巫师还没来得及说话呢
I mean, the wizard would get shot between the eyes
就已经被爆头了
before he could ever get out the words,
比利小子究竟去
"What the hell is Billy the Kid doing
卡亚秘境干嘛
in the mystic realm of Ka'a?"
莱纳德
Leonard...
谢尔顿和他朋友艾米是啥关系
What's the deal with Sheldon's friend Amy?
他们是一对吗
Are they a couple?
一对怪人倒是真的  怎么了
Couple of weirdos. Why?
你对艾米感兴趣吗
You interested in Amy?
我只是觉得她看我的时候
Well, I mean, she didn't look through me
不会觉得我灵魂恶心  胆小如鼠
with soul-sucking, ball-shriveling
也不会一脸厌恶和鄙夷
hatred and contempt.
我喜欢这种女人
I like that in a woman.
能否帮我问问谢尔顿  我能不能约她出去玩
Could you run it by Sheldon if I could ask her out?
当然可以
Sure. I guess.
斯图尔特  帮我们解决下争议
Stuart, settle an argument for us.
谁会赢
Who would win,
比利小子还是白袍巫师
Billy the Kid or the White Wizard?
我要是告诉你们
If I tell you that,
我就剥夺了你们玩这个游戏的快乐
I'm robbing you of the hours of fun you could have
现在超低价  只卖24块9毛5哦
for the magical, rootin'-tootin' low price of $24.95.
我要一个
I'll take one.
那  要两个吧
Mm... make it two.
我恨你们和我自己  要三个
I hate all of you and myself. Three.
我去下单
I'll ring it up.
瓮中捉鳖  易如反掌
Like shooting nerds in a barrel.
生活大爆炸第五季第十集
我能跟你谈件事吗
Hey, can I talk to you about something?
有点难开口
It's a little awkward.
我知道你要说什么
I know what this is about.
鉴于你事业上的停滞不前
Given the professional standstill you're at,
你现在肯定想知道是否应该
you're wondering if this is the appropriate time
放弃科研  专攻教育事业
to abandon your research and focus on teaching.
应该
Yes.
而且我建议你
And if I may suggest,
考虑教别的学科
consider changing disciplines.
比如人文学科  就像历史
Yeah, to the humanities-- perhaps history.
教历史的一个好处在于
One of the advantages of teaching history
你不用搞创造发明
is that you don't have to create things.
你只要记住历史上发生过的事
You know, you just have to remember stuff that happened
然后鹦鹉学舌般复述就行
and then parrot it back.
你会觉得很开心的
You could have fun with that.
我要说的不是这个
Yeah, that's not it.
斯图尔特对艾米感兴趣
Stuart's kind of interested in Amy.
这当然啦  她是非常有趣的人
Oh, of course he is. She's very interesting.
你知道吗  她14岁的时候
Did you know, when she was 14,
自己把脚趾间连着的皮割开了
she severed the webbing between her own toes?
不是这个意思
No.
他叫我问问
He wanted me to find out
你介不介意他约艾米出去玩
if you'd have a problem with him asking her out.
我不确定该怎么回答  莱纳德
I'm not sure how to respond, Leonard.
艾米又不是我的人
I don't own Amy.
我也不能拥有某个人
Can't own a person.
至少从什么时候开始不能呢
At least not since...
1863年
1863.
因为林肯总统解放了什么呢
President Lincoln freed the...
黑奴  拜托  莱纳德
Slaves! Come on, Leonard,
如果你要去教历史
if you're going to teach history,
你就该知道这些历史事件
these are the kind of facts you'll have to know.
好吧  当我没说
You know what? Never mind.
我就让他放心大胆地去约艾米吧
I'm going to tell him it's okay to ask her out.
这问题毫无意义
The question is moot.
斯图尔特这么一个
There is no way that Stuart,
穷不啦叽的漫画店老板
an impoverished peddler of picture books,
对艾米·菲拉·福勒毫无吸引力可言
would be at all appealing to Amy Farrah Fowler,
她可是著名神经生理学家
a noted neurobiologist
只用罐子里的鲜奶油做出的
capable of performing surgery on her own feet
一氧化二氮有轻微麻醉作用 并致人发笑
一氧化二氮当麻醉剂
with nothing but nitrous oxide
就能给自己的脚动手术
from cans of whipped cream as anesthesia.
好吧  不过强调一下
All right, but for the record,
我可是特意征询过你对此事的感受
I checked in with you to see how you'd feel about it.
知道了  我已经如实回答了
Fine. The record shall so reflect.
现在我们回到要紧的问题上
Now, getting back to the problem at hand,
失败的实验物理学家应该怎么办...
what to do with a washed-up experimental physicist...
我没有失败
I am not washed-up.
莱纳德
Oh, Leonard.
有很多人关心你  想帮助你
Lots of people love you and want to help you,
但除非你正视自己的问题  否则都是徒劳
but they can't until you admit the problem.
姑娘们  我们喝完了一瓶
Well, ladies, we killed the bottle.
我只喝了半杯
I had half a glass.
- 我一点都没喝上  -好吧  别怪我
- I didn't have any. - Okay, don't judge me.
你们想玩什么
So, what do you want to do--
看电影  去跳舞  还是去躺一会
go to the movies, go dancing, lay down for a little bit?
或者我们可以玩扭扭乐
Or we play... Travel Twister.
真的吗  艾米  扭扭乐
Amy, really? Twister?
拜托  扭扭乐伴我度过了无数个美好的夜晚
Excuse me. I've passed many an enjoyable evening playing this game.
而且我觉得和别人一起玩
And I'm sure it's a lot more exciting
肯定更有趣
when you play with other people.
怎么样  闺蜜  我们分成穿衣队和不穿衣队
What do you say, bestie? We can do shirts and skins.
我是穿衣队  不好意思先挑咯
I'm shirts. Called it.
我太娇小了  不能玩扭扭乐
I'm too small for Twister.
过山车也不行
And roller coasters.
坐着的时候脚也够不到地上
And sitting with my feet on the floor.
都怪你怀孕的时候抽烟  妈妈
Hope you enjoyed the prenatal cigarettes, Mom.
我妈妈怀孕的时候也抽烟
Hey, you know, my mom smoked pot when she was pregnant with me,
但我身心发育完好
and I turned out just fine.
瞧  还有蜜桃酒呢
Hey, look, I have peach schnapps.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
姑娘们  出事了
Guys, something happened.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我觉得有个男生喜欢我
I think a boy likes me.
你好  我是斯图尔特
"Hi. It's Stuart.
我们在漫画店里见过
"We met at the comic book store.
不知道我能不能约你出来喝杯咖啡
"I was wondering if you'd like to get coffee sometime.
你拒绝也没关系
"It's okay if you say no.
就是这打击有点大
"It might be the kick in the pants I need
没准我得去吃片舍曲林[抗焦虑药物]
to start taking Zoloft."
艾米  你个小狐狸精
Amy, little vixen.
衣服穿这么多  还挡不住你的骚气呀
Just working it under all those layers of wool and polyester.
你要怎么办
What are you going to do?
他不知道你有男朋友了吗
Doesn't he know you have a boyfriend?
她有的不是男朋友
Oh, she doesn't have a boyfriend;
是谢尔顿
she has a Sheldon.
你喜欢斯图尔特吗
So do you like Stuart?
我不知道
I don't know.
他人不错
He's nice.
挺风趣
He's funny.
就是有些面黄肌瘦
He has the sallow, drawn countenance
还有活跃得不太正常的甲状腺
associated with an overactive thyroid gland.
那还挺性感的
That's kind of hot.
好吧  亲爱的  我们都喜欢谢尔顿
Okay, look, sweetie, we all love Sheldon,
但你和他一起都一年多了
but you've been with him over a year now.
如果没有新进展
If it's not going anywhere,
何不发展新恋情呢
what does it hurt to look around?
就是  他们也没订婚  不像我和华仔
Well, yeah, I guess they're not engaged like me and Howie.
好吧  不管怎样
Yeah, for what it's worth,
就算订了婚也可以反悔的
engaged people can look around, too.
外面的世界很精彩哦
Lot of options out there.
斯图尔特呢
Where's Stuart?
出去了
Out.
你是谁
Who are you?
戴尔
I'm Dale.
他让我看店
He left me in charge.
真的吗
Really?
是的
Yeah.
我也搞不懂
I don't get it, either.
我想退掉这个
I want to return this
"荒野西部与卡亚女巫"的扩展包
"Wild West and Witches Ka'a" expansion pack.
抱歉  我不处理退货
Sorry. I don't do returns.
太难了
They're hard.
当然
Sure, sure.
斯图尔特什么时候回来
Uh, when will Stuart be back?
我不知道  他出去喝咖啡了
I don't know. He went out for coffee.
和个女孩一起哟
With a girl.
我想我错了
Oh, I guess I was wrong.
你还好吧
You okay?
我还好吧
Am I okay?
莱纳德  我这辈子迟早会拿诺贝尔奖
Leonard, I'm on a lifelong trajectory
有座城市还要以我的名字命名
that includes a Nobel Prize and cities named after me,
我的四颗智齿
all four wisdom teeth
在我嘴里安稳地长着  完全不用拔掉
fit comfortably in my mouth without need of extraction,
我的肠道活动就像德国火车一样规律
and my bowel movements run like a German train schedule.
你说我还好吗
Am I okay?
那我也很好
I'm okay, too!
荒野女巫柯克
Wild Bill Witchcock.
阿布拉-科曼切部落
A tribe of Abra-Comanches.
燃烧的痰盂
Flaming Spittoon.
强调一下
And for the record,
我对你们这些牛仔很失望
I'm very disappointed in you cowpokes.
这是咱们第一次玩"狂野西部女巫"
We're playing our inaugural round of "Wild West and Witches" ,
居然只有我一个人
and I'm the only one
费尽苦心地穿了应景的服装
who bothered to dress for the occasion.
我呸
Patooie.
我们才不要戴牛仔帽呢  谢尔顿
We're not wearing cowboy hats, Sheldon.
看起来好白痴
It looks ridiculous.
这么说我的靴子和马刺也很白痴咯
And I suppose my boots and spurs are ridiculous, too?
-是的  -非常白痴  -超级白痴
- Yeah.  - Very.  - Incredibly so.
那咱们上次玩"撒旦动物"时
Did it look ridiculous when we got the Satanimals pack
我装扮成"恶魔猫"也很白痴吗
and I dressed up as a Beelzebobcat?
-是的  -非常白痴  -超级白痴
- Yeah.  - Very.  - Incredibly so.
好吧  算了  咱就纯玩吧
All right, fine. Let's just play.
咱们今天晚上就饶了他吧
We should go easy on him.
艾米今晚跟斯图尔特出去了
Amy's out with Stuart tonight.
等会
Wait a minute.
你是说谢尔顿的不可一世
Are you telling me that Sheldon's patented blend
和无性交往的专利
of condescension and no sex
留不住一个女人吗
isn't enough to hold on to a woman?
傻笑  傻笑  傻笑
Cluck, cluck, cluck.
咱是聚在一起缝棉被的家庭妇女吗
What are we, ladies at a quilting bee?
还是正在玩一个背景设在魔幻边境的
Or are we men playing a fantasy card game
魔幻桌游的一群男人
set in a magical frontier town?
抱歉
Sorry.
诡异帐篷
Creepy Tepee.
奇丑安妮
Annie Ogly.
魔幻波卡洪塔斯[印第安公主]
Hocus Pocus Pocahontas.
容我说一句  你们仨
And may I point out it is the three of you
真是皇帝不急  太监急
who are obsessed with Stuart and Amy, not me.
你们才该扪心自问一下
I think you need to ask yourselves
究竟谁才是白痴
who's really being ridiculous here.
-你  -是你  -绝对是你
- It's you.  - You are.  - Totally you.
伙计们  看呀
Hey, guys, check it out.
这是装在金属盒里  附上签名的
The deluxe limited edition "Wild West and Witches"
豪华限量版的"狂野西部女巫"
expansion pack in the signed and numbered collector's tin.
不是吧
Come on, no!
我们刚买了平装版
We just bought the regular pack.
是警徽
Ooh, a sheriff's badge.
没错  还是根魔杖
Yeah, it's also a wand.
还有全息图呢  真漂亮
With a hologram? Nice!
你看见没
Hey, do you see this?
我在矩阵里  莱纳德  我什么都看得见
I'm in the matrix, Leonard; I see everything.
你搞什么
You got to be kidding me.
你在Facebook加了斯图尔特为好友
You friended Stuart on Facebook?
你不是不喜欢玩Facebook了嘛
I thought you didn't like Facebook anymore.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
我喜欢一切试图取代
I'm a fan of anything that tries to
人类面对面接触的东西
replace actual human contact.
拜托
Please.
你上Facebook就为看他们约会得如何
You're looking at Facebook to find out how their date went.
真的吗
Really?
我觉得我会关心一个大男人
You think I care if a man, what,
"跟一位绝世美女分享一杯南瓜拿铁"吗
"shared a pumpkin latte with a dynamite lady"?
你真是醋劲十足
You're so full of it.
随便你怎么想
You are free to believe whatever you like.
取消和拉杰什·库萨帕里的好友关系
And unfriend Rajesh Koothrappali.
你取消了和我的好友关系  真的吗
You unfriended me? Seriously?
这下坏了
Oh, yeah.
他这下就要错过你的精彩更新了  像是
Now he's gonna miss all those great updates like,
"我真不敢相信我居然等了这么久
"I can't believe I waited this long
才整理出我的个人文集“
to make my own potpourri"
谢尔顿  你何不直接承认
Sheldon, why don't you just acknowledge
你喜欢艾米
that you have feelings for Amy
而且你不想她跟其他男人约会呢
and you don't want her going out with other men?
解除和莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德的好友关系
And unfriend Leonard Hofstadter.
我有个激进点的主意
Here's a radical thought.
你干脆采取老一套  跟斯图尔特决斗吧
Go old-school, challenge Stuart to a fight.
没有什么能比两个瘦骨嶙峋的白人男子
I mean, nothing makes the ladies hotter
闭着眼猛敲对方
than two skinny white guys
更能让一个女人热血沸腾的了
swatting at each other with their eyes closed.
解除与霍华德·沃罗威茨的好友关系
And unfriend Howard Wolowitz.
咱们都被删了
That's all of us.
-电脑借我用一下吧  -干嘛
- Can I use the laptop?  - Why?
我要买那个傻逼收集版的游戏
I have to buy that stupid collector's tin.
-我们大家都爱谁  -佩妮
- Who do we love?  - Penny.
你好呀  谢尔顿
Hello, Sheldon.
进来吧
Come on in.
-谢谢  -怎么了
- Thank you.  - What's up?
我是来问你  愿不愿意跟我约会的
I came to ask if you would like to go on a date with me.
抱歉  你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
约会
A date.
你跟我
You and me.
共进晚餐  跳舞
Dining, dancing,
没准你会有兴趣参加个职业拳击赛什么的
perhaps you'd like to take in a prizefight.
天啊  你是想让艾米吃醋吗
God, are you trying to make Amy jealous?
不是
No.
为何大家这么关心艾米和斯图尔特呢
Why is everyone so obsessed with Amy and Stuart?
讨论他们今晚是否会继续喝南瓜拿铁
Whether or not they may be having more pumpkin lattes
或今晚是否会发生关系
or intercourse tonight.
好吧  听我说
Okay, listen to me.
耍把戏是不会帮你把艾米抢回来的
Playing games is not gonna help get Amy back.
我没准备把她抢回来
I am not trying to get her back.
不过  纯属好奇  怎么才能把她抢回来呢
But, out of curiosity, what is a way?
好吧  亲爱的  我给你讲个故事吧
All right, honey, let me tell you a story.
我喜欢过一个男人  但从未对他表白过
There was a guy I liked, and I never told him how I felt.
最终他开始跟别人约会
Eventually, he started going out with someone else,
于是我一直很后悔
and I always regretted it.
你明白我的意思了吗
Do you see where I'm going with this?
我想是的
I believe I do.
我就是你暗恋的那个人
I'm the guy.
不是你
You're not the guy.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
这就解释了一切
That would explain so much.
你总是赖在我家不走
Your constant presence in my apartment,
你和莱纳德厮混也只是为了靠近我
that baffling dalliance with Leonard just to be near me,
还有你一直叫我"亲爱的"
the way you call me "sweetie" all the time.
我见谁都叫"亲爱的"
I call everyone "sweetie."
你个荡妇
You tramp.
谢尔顿  我的意思是
Look, Sheldon, all I'm saying is
带点种  去找艾米谈谈吧
strap on a pair and go talk to Amy.
带什么
"Strap on a pair"?
系鞋带吗
Of what, skates?
亲爱的  绝对不是你
Oh, sweetie, you are so not the guy.
无聊的话  你可以先走
If you're bored, you can go.
我完全理解
I understand.
不  我看得很开心
No, I'm having a nice time.
别屈尊安慰我了
Don't patronize me.
抱歉  借过
Excuse me. Excuse me.
不好意思
Pardon me.
不好意思  借过
Pardon me. Excuse me.
嗨  斯图尔特
Hi, Stuart.
嗨  谢尔顿
Hi, Sheldon.
借过一下  不好意思
Pardon me... Excuse me...
谢尔顿  你来干嘛
Sheldon, what are you doing here?
我只要一想到你跟斯图尔特那厮
The thought of you sitting in a darkened theater
坐在漆黑的影院中  一股厌恶之情就油然而生
with a character like Stuart is repellent.
无意冒犯  斯图尔特
No offense, Stuart.
我没在意
None taken.
虽然"厌恶"这词儿...有点重了
Although "repellent" is kind of a... kind of a strong word.
抱歉让你不快了
I'm sorry this causes you discomfort,
但基于我们关系目前的既定参数
but based on the currently established parameters of our relationship,
只要我乐意  我可以做任何让你厌恶的事情
I can put myself in any repellent situation I want.
我再说一遍...
Um, again...
拜托  斯图尔特  你这样很无礼
Stuart, please. You're being rude.
还有什么话要说吗
Anything else?
我想改变我俩的关系模式
I believe I would like to alter the paradigm of our relationship.
我洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
基于无论如何都维持原状的共识
With the understanding that nothing changes whatsoever,
包括身体或其他方面
physical or otherwise,
我将不会不同意
I would not object to
也不再把你定位为"不是我女朋友"
us no longer characterizing you as "not my girlfriend."
有意思
Interesting.
现在把"不"字去掉再给我说一遍
Now try it without the quadruple negative.
你别得寸进尺
You're being impossible.
嗨  斯图尔特
Hi, Stuart.
好吧
Fine.
艾米
Amy...
你愿意做我女朋友吗
will you be my girlfriend?
-愿意  -好  这样就够了
- Yes.  - Well, that's enough of that.
抱歉打扰你们了
Sorry to interrupt.
祝两位约会愉快
You two enjoy your date.
给你一块钱  就当我给你添麻烦了
Here's a dollar for your troubles.
自己去买点酸软糖吃吧
Get yourself some Sour Patch Kids.
不好意思  借过一下  抱歉
Excuse me... Excuse me... Pardon me...
除了让你和另一个家伙的关系
So, other than you taking your relationship
更近一步之外  今晚还是很美好的
to the next level with another guy, this was nice.
是啊  谢谢送我到家门口
Yes, well, thanks for seeing me to my door.
不客气
Oh, you're welcome.
艾米  艾米  艾米
Amy. Amy. Amy.
外面解决好再进门
Let's wrap things up out there.
晚安  斯图尔特
Um, good night, Stuart.
晚安
Good night.
别装傻了  斯图尔特
Take the hint, Stuart.
人家都说晚安了
The lady said "Good night."
你怎么进来我家的
How did you get into my apartment?
是不是你成了我女朋友
Is that the kind of nagging I can expect
从今往后我就要听这种唠叨呀
now that you're my girlfriend?
幸好我起草好合同了
Good thing I drew this up.
那是什么
What's that?
我给你拿来了《恋爱合同》
I present to you the relationship agreement.
这是份有约束力的契约书  在这31页里
A binding covenant that, in its 31 pages,
列举  重申并整理出
enumerates, iterates and codifies
谢尔顿·李·库珀的权利与义务
the rights and responsibilities of Sheldon Lee Cooper,
以下简称"男友"
here and after known as "the boyfriend,"
艾米·菲拉·福勒的权利义务
and Amy Farrah Fowler,
以下简称"女友"
here and after known as "the girlfriend""
这真是太浪漫了
It's so romantic.
你我一向都是相补的
Mutual indemnification always is.
在我准备公证人印章时  你可以开始阅读条款了
Why don't you start perusing while I set up my notary stamp.
第五条  牵手
"Section 5: Hand-holding.
牵手仅允许在
"Hand-holding is only allowed
以下情况中发生:
under the following circumstances.
A  任何一方身处坠落悬崖
"A: Either party is in danger of falling off a cliff,
绝壁或暗礁的危险时
precipice or ledge;
B  在任何一方赢得诺贝尔奖时
B: Either party is deserving of a hearty handshake
必须衷心握手庆贺
after winning a Nobel Prize;
C  感冒时给予精神支持时
C: Moral support during flu shots"
这条条框框也太多了吧
Seems a bit restrictive.
尽管去找律师好了
Feel free to retain a lawyer.
佩妮  我说的是"右手红色"
Penny, I said "right hand red."
对  我听到了
Yeah, I heard you.
我碰到红[酒]了
I got red.
伯纳黛特  左脚黄色
Bernadette, left foot yellow.
《地狱边境》  2D水墨风格解迷游戏
接下来我们该玩《地狱边境》
We should play limbo next.
没人玩得过我
No one beats me at limbo.
佩妮  艾米  伯纳黛特
Penny. Amy. Bernadette.
是我男朋友
That's my boyfriend.
门没关
It's open!
我手指破了
I got a splinter.
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do about it?
《恋爱合同》第四条  小伤小痛
Relationship agreement Section 4: Boo-boos and Ouchies.
你得照顾它
You have to take care of it.
我真该找个律师的
I should've gotten a lawyer.
看来就剩咱俩玩了
Looks like it's just us playing.
佩妮
Penny?
佩妮  酒都喝光啦
Penny, we're out of wine!
你赶紧开车去买吧
You should probably drive.